### Stephanie Aurelio

Hello.

LOS ANGELES, CA
PHONE
916-420-0772

E-MAIL

stephanie.m.aurelio@gmail.com

#### PROFILE

Ex-librarian turned developer with a background in libraries and museums. Adept at learning new tech, research, information organization/visualization, and collaborative work environments. Experienced with databases and information management systems. Currently pursuing education in full-stack development through UCLA Extension.

#### EXPERIENCE

### LIBRARIAN, CITY OF SANTA MONICA; SANTA MONICA, CA

NOV 2018 - AUG 2019

Developed, marketed, and implemented programs in accordance with outcomes-based metrics and survey data. Reference services, tech instruction, and system-wide event planning. Managed teen volunteer program.

### LIBRARIAN, CITY OF MONROVIA; MONROVIA, CA SEP 2017 - OCT 2018

Grant writing and management for public programming. Collection development, materials cataloging, and classification. Volunteer management.

## LIBRARIAN, SACRAMENTO PUBLIC LIBRARY, SACRAMENTO, CA MAY 2015 - JULY 2017

Community collaborator with a focus on building partnerships to provide innovative, health-based programming for a library in a Building Healthy Communities promise zone. Outreach to schools, parent groups, and community centers.

# MEMBERSHIP ASSISTANT, CROCKER ART MUSEUM; SACRAMENTO, CA NOV 2013 - JAN 2015

Database management for member/donation database charged with adding, editing, and merging records, running reports, and exporting data. Wrote database best practices for training new hires. Collaborated with departments on member events.

### EDUCATION

# SAN JOSE STATE UNIVERSITY; SAN JOSE, CA MASTER'S, LIBRARY AND INFORMATION SCIENCE - 2015 CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, SACRAMENTO; SACRAMENTO, CA BACHELOR OF ARTS, HISTORY - 2010

### SKILLS

- · Windows & Mac OS, Microsoft Office Suite, Google suite
- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, Git

CONNECT

LINKEDIN GITHUB

linkedin.com/in/stephaniemaurelio/ github.com/stephmarie17/portfolio